cokeandpopcorn.com 2012-10-17

# Coke & Popcorn > Privacy Policy

###  Privacy Policy

We take the privacy of our users very seriously. Here we explain in detail what information we collect from you and how we use that information. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, please check this page periodically to learn about any new changes.

**1\. Personal Information**  
When trying to post comments, you may have to provide some personal information about yourself, such as your name and email. You can also add an avatar (personal image) or build a profile to share with our other users. Our comment plugin system is powered by DISQUS, please visit their site to learn more about their terms We will not share your email with any third party. We will use your email to send notifications to you. We may send a cookie to your browser so our comment system can remember you and make posting comments easier in the future.

**2\. Statistical (Non-personal) Information**  
We often collect non-personal information to help us serve our users better. This includes things like your browser, operating system, ISP etc. This information is used by us for making Cokeandpopcorn.com more compatible and user-friendly for you.

**3\. Third Party Content**  
Cokeandpopcorn.com contains many links to other websites. Many of these links are posted by our users and we have no control over the content on these third party websites. 

**4\. Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).   
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
